candefashions.com 2013-04-25

# C & E Fashions | World's Best Men's Dress Shoes

C&E Fashions is committed to respecting your privacy rights. The following policy describes how we collect, protect and use information we receive from you.

We are responsible for this privacy policy. Please note, however, that any third party websites you may enter through C&E Fashions may have different privacy policies. We highly recommend that you read the policies of these websites. 

#### What information do we collect?

  * We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order and respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. 
  * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, date of birth, e-mail address, mailing address, daytime phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously or purchase without registering. 
  * C&E Fashions receives store click-stream data and other information about visits to our websites which may be combined with personal information you have provided. This information is used to analyze and improve your online shopping experience. For more information see the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below. 

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use other site features in the following ways: 

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 
  * To quickly process your transactions. 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 
  * If you have opted-in to receive C&E Fashions e-mail, or completed an online order, we may send you periodic e-mails from C&E Fashions. If you would no longer like to receive C&E Fashions e-mail, please refer to the “How can you remove or modify information you have provided to us?” section below. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' contents will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us. 

#### How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you provide us with is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and stored into our databases to be accessed as stated above. Currently, only the last four digits of credit card numbers are saved in our database.

####  Do we use “cookies”?

No. C&E Fashions uses temporary PHP sessions to store shopping cart information which is dumped once you leave the C&E Fashions web site (some browsers may have to be closed for all session data to be dumped), or you complete an order. Information from your session is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

### Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties unless we provide you with an advance notice, except as described below. The term “outside parties” does not include C&E Fashions company or web sites. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting C&E Fashions's business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### How can you remove or modify information you have provided to us?

If you would like to unsubscribe from our mailing list , and remove or modify your profile you may use our online contact form. Simply submit your request to customer support desk. Use form field "Your questions or comments" to provide us with new information or tape in "remove me" to delete your profile from our database. You also can email us at [info@candefashions.com](mailto:info@candefashions.com). When submitting your request do not forget to specify your full name and address associated with your profile. This will help us to process your request faster. 

#### Changes to our policy

This policy was last modified on December 3, 2007. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

####  Questions and feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please email us at [info@candefashions.com](mailto:info@candefashions.com).

#### Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
